## **Phil Perry**

Senior Javascript Developer at Atlassian

### Summary

Senior front-end web developer & designer with a passion for the web and it's ever-developing technologies. Strong background in graphic / web design and digital advertising on both small screens (mobile to desktops) and large (billboards). Well versed in Agile development, E-commerce, user-experience design, responsive web design, analytics and integrations. High proficiency in front-end technologies, tools, libraries and frameworks including Angular, React, Flux, Backbone, jQuery, Sass, Grunt, Gulp and the like. Familiar with various server-side tools and tech including Node (Express) and Python (Django).

## Experience

#### Senior Javascript Developer - HipChat at Atlassian

June 2015 - Present

#### **Designer and Developer**

January 2001 - Present

Freelance graphic and web design development for a variety of local clients in both the Baton Rouge, LA and Pensacola, FL areas. Design projects ranged from branding and logo design, business cards, brochures, and out of home campaigns. Web projects included simple static websites, Wordpress and Drupal theme design and development, and Django development.

#### Senior Front-End Web Developer - Marketplace and Purchasing Platforms at Atlassian

January 2014 - June 2015 (1 year 5 months)

#### Front-End Web Developer - Interactive Marketing at Atlassian

January 2013 - December 2013 (11 months)

Responsible for development of atlassian.com's angularJS shopping cart applications:

- \* https://www.atlassian.com/purchase
- \* https://www.atlassian.com/ondemand/signup

Manage dependencies, builds and releases using appropriate tools such as Yeoman, Bower & Grunt. Wrote custom build automation scripts using Grunt and python. Managed source control of project repositories using Git together with Bitbucket

Work with Project Managers and Designers on A/B testing, integration with analytics, continuous iteration to improve the purchase flow.

#### Senior Front End Web Developer at Lamar Advertising Company

#### March 2009 - January 2013 (3 years 10 months)

Created and maintained custom Javascript framework to manage ajax requests, caching, logging, sharing variables between Javascript and Scalascript, and common utils.

Train and oversee other iSpot team members.

Continue to drive the digital outdoor offerings forward by staying on top of web trends and technologies.

#### Front End Designer / Developer at Lamar Advertising Company

August 2006 - March 2009 (2 years 7 months)

Front end design and development of digital billboard ads that integrate with client websites and/or social media to display live, dynamic data (referred to at Lamar as "iSpots") using a combination of Javascript, Python, Scalascript (www.scala.com), XML and JSON.

Developed various forms of automation for the creation of these dynamic spots using Javascript, XML and XSL to automatically generate the common scripts behind them.

Offer technical support for the sales force and point man between them and the Network Operations Center to troubleshoot problems and train clients on proprietary systems.

#### **Graphic Designer at Lamar Advertising Company**

July 2003 - August 2006 (3 years 1 month)

Worked in central art department for nationwide company doing Graphic Design work for businesses across the country.

Increased productivity and speed of the art department by using Javascript and Extendscript (Adobe extension of ECMAScript for Photoshop automation) to leverage the Photoshop DOM to automate all the redundant steps of the artist workflow; including the creation of templates and dynamic building of online proofs using XML/XMP metadata.

#### Education

#### **Louisiana State University**

BFA, Graphic Design, 1999 - 2003

# **Phil Perry**

Senior Javascript Developer at Atlassian



Contact Phil on LinkedIn